Retirement didn't suit him.
Freelance is a action, comedy film directed by Pierre Morel.
An ex-special forces operative takes a job to provide security for a journalist as she interviews a dictator, but a military
coup breaks out in the middle of the interview, they are forced to escape into the jungle where they must survive.
Mason Pettits, played by John Cena.
Claire Wellington, played by Alison Brie.
President Juan Venegas, played by Juan Pablo Raba.
Sebastian Earle, played by Christian Slater.
Jenny Pettits, played by Alice Eve.
Colonel Jan Koehorst, played by Marton Csokas.
Freelance is a 2023 American action comedy film directed by Pierre Morel
and written by Jacob Lentz in his feature writing debut.
It stars John Cena, Alison Brie, Juan Pablo Raba, and Christian Slater.
The film was released by Relativity Media on October
27, 2023, grossing $10.2 million.
The film explores themes of coup d'etat, dictatorship, political
assassination, duringcreditsstinger, investigative journalism.
The tone is lighthearted.